<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!--SKETCHES/DRAWINGS-->

    <!--Sombra-->
    <string name="sombraTitle">Sombra</string>
    <string name="sombraDescription">Medium: Colored Pencil, Ink Pen\nSombra is a character from the game Overwatch. I really loved one of her alternate designs, and this is the result of that. Cyberpunk chinstrap!</string>

    <!--Simon Pegg-->
    <string name="peggTitle">Simon Pegg</string>
    <string name="peggDescription">Medium: Charcoal/Pastel\nArt project from high school. If you haven\'t seen Hot Fuzz, do yourself a favour.</string>

    <!--Jimmy Page-->
    <string name="pageTitle">Jimmy Page</string>
    <string name="pageDescription">Medium: Charcoal/Pastel\nCommission done in high school for a friend. I\'m particularly proud of the way the leather looks on the jacket.</string>

    <!--Street-->
    <string name="streetTitle">Konbini</string>
    <string name="streetDescription">Medium: Ink Pen\nA cozy little scene of a convenience store nestled in a residential area. While I don\'t think this is my best drawing, I find it very relaxing to look at.</string>


    <!--PAINTINGS-->

    <!--Iron Man-->
    <string name="ironmanTitle">Iron Man</string>
    <string name="ironmanDescription">Medium: Acrylic on Canvas\nThis was done for a friend of mine. I\'m fairly proud of the lighting and texture that parts of this painting achieve. Iron man is the best Avenger too.</string>

    <!--Pupper-->
    <string name="pupperTitle">Shiba Inu</string>
    <string name="pupperDescription">Medium: Watercolor pencils\nA cute little Shiba. I don\'t have one, so I draw one.</string>

    <!--Beach-->
    <string name="beachTitle">Virginia Beach</string>
    <string name="beachDescription">Based on the view from a hotel in Virginia beach, not too far from the poseidon statue (That I also painted! Wacko!).</string>

    <!--Snowfall-->
    <string name="snowfallTitle">Winter</string>
    <string name="snowfallDescription">A recreation of the work \'Winter\', done by Lawren Harris. I found the combination of colours really captivating.</string>


    <!--DIGITAL-->

    <!--Dark Elf-->
    <string name="darkelfTitle">Dark Elf</string>
    <string name="darkelfDescription">Medium: Digital, Apple Pen\nI got the chance to try out the Apple pen, and I gotta say it\'s pretty fun to use. The subject is a generic dark elf from the Elder Scrolls series of games.</string>

</resources>